Mohit Maddhesiya

Mahadevapura Bangalore, Karnataka, 560048

Summary

I possess very good programming skills as well as the ability to develop multiple logics for solutions. Using any particular programming language has never been a bar for me yet my area of expertise are Java programming language and JavaScript

Experience

o Software Developer @ Crisp Analytics Pvt. Ltd, Noida

June 2015 - October 2016

- Working as a Data processing layer.
- Collecting, filtering and cleaning data
- Module wise development using nodejs and angularjs.
- o Intern @ Crisp Analytics Pvt. Ltd, Noida

January 2015 - June 2015

- Module wise development using codeigniter.

Technical Competencies

o Programming Languages: Proficient in: Java, Php, JavaScript, HTML.

Industry Software / Framework: AngularJS, NodeJs, Ionic, Spring, Kafka, Storm, Maven, Codeigniter, Bootstrap, Git

Databases: Mysql , Postgres

o Environment: Linux, Eclipse, Tomcat

Other: Data Structures

Projects

Tikali Energy Usage Profiling :

A project to detect anomalies in power consumption at 1000s of locations in France and US. Energy Consumption Profiling based on predictive and statistical analysis.

Stanmax :

Merchandise planning based on historical analysis .Retail Merchandiser Planning System that is plan for goods and area for future based on last year and last to last year. Merchandiser analyze data, to set selling price, plan promotions and price reduction. Reporting tool for a retail store for their transactions.

Grap Education :

Grap Education is an e-commerce website. It provides online courses.

o FastPay :

The project focuses at providing an easy and reliable platform to recharge mobile number of any telecommunication company through an android app without buying a recharge card.

o IMS CHAI:

IMS CHAI web application that is designed to track the inventory of Pharmaceutical suppliers to DAC from suppliers through to end users (patients) including dispensation to patients.

Education

Master of Computer Application

2012-2015

National Institute of Technology (NIT), Kurukshetra, (CGPA: 7.89/10.00)

Bachelor of Computer Application

2008-2011

Maharshi Dayanand University, Rohtak, (65.73%)

Interests and extra-curricular activity

- o Programming Languages: have been a constant stalker of hackerearth and geeksforgeeks
- o Playing Badminton: have got district level winner.

References

Vaibhav Dobriyal

Vice President Research and Development | Crisp Analytics Mobile: +91.8527116444 | Email: vaibhav@crispanalytics.com